<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Capsule</string>
    <string name="back_icon_desc">Back</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="notes">Notes</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="note_title">The Bat’s Echolocation</string>
    <string name="note_body">\n
        Although bats can see, in order to sense their surroundings in the darkness of night, most species use echolocation—determining the distance of an object by means of reflected sound. For example, some bats can distinguish a mosquito from a beetle by the speed of the insect’s wing beats.\n\n
        Most bats produce pulses of sound in their larynx and project them through their mouth or nostrils. They use their large ears to detect the echoes produced when the sound waves rebound off objects. These echoes enable a bat to build a mental 3D image of its surroundings. The bat is able to determine the location, elevation, and distance of an object, even amid the noise clutter produced by other bats.\n\n
        The bat’s echolocation needs to be extremely precise because an error of just one millisecond (one-thousandth of a second) could cause the bat to miss its target by as much as 17 centimeters (6.7 in). According to some researchers, a precision greater than one millisecond “appears impossible.” Yet, experiments suggest that bats have an echo time precision of 10 nanoseconds (100,000,000th of a second), enabling them to determine distances with an accuracy of a millimeter or even less!</string>
    <string name="up_next">Up Next:</string>
    <string name="quiz_test">Quiz Test</string>
    <string name="ten_questions">Questions: 10</string>
    <string name="notes_description">Read about The Bat’s Echolocation</string>
    <string name="start_quiz_button">Start Quiz Test</string>
    <string name="quiz_result">Result</string>
    <string name="no_result_yet">Complete and submit quiz test to see result</string>
    <string name="questions_tag">Question %d/%d</string>
    <string name="help_icon_desc">Help</string>
    <string name="question">Q%d. %s</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next question</string>
    <string name="prev_button">Previous question</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="score_text">Score: </string>
    <string name="not_good">Not good.\nYou can do better.</string>
    <string name="fair">A fair result with room for improvement.</string>
    <string name="satisfactory">Satisfactory performance</string>
    <string name="very_good">A very good result.\nWell-done!</string>
    <string name="excellent">An excellent performance!\nYou were so close to acing it.</string>
    <string name="congratulations">CONGRATULATIONS!\nYou aced it like you wrote it. 🥳</string>
    <string name="statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="number_of_questions">Number of questions: %d</string>
    <string name="questions_answered">Questions answered: %d</string>
    <string name="correct_answers_given">Correct answers: %d</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help1">In order to save time, you can skip questions that seem tough and return to them before submission.\n\n
        Once you submit your answers, you will be directed to the Result screen.</string>
    <string name="help2">Reset result to take quiz again.</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="welcome_greeting">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Please watch the video before proceeding.\nAfter which, read the note on the next screen\n
        Then you will be equipped to attempt the 10 questions that follow as they are based on either the video, note or general knowledge.\n
        You are to complete all screens before the allotted 10 minutes.\n\n
        Your time starts when you start.</string>
    <string name="start_button">START</string>
</resources>